Name: 李梓琦 LI ZIQI Mobile Number: +86 1327 5922 779 E-Mail: liziqi_@hotmail.com

Profile

Through the study overseas and the multi-nation working experience from the past 13 years, I trained myself to be a highly self-motivated, task-oriented, open-minded and someone who is willing to spend extra to learn new skill-sets to meet the demands of my job.

Based on the most recent working experience, which has the different cultural background, I have learned more professional workspaces rules and better manage the workplace relationship for different cultural background, most importantly, I have a better understanding about my abilities and passions.

I am looking for a full-time job as a software developer, where I hope to be an asset to the company with my skills and experience.

| Education Information | | | | |
|-----------------------|----------------------------------|-----------------------------|-------------|--|
| 07.2014 - 12.2017 | Nanyang Technological University | Computer Engineering | Degree | |
| 03.2011 - 04.2014 | Singapore Polytechnic | Info-Communication & Design | Diploma | |
| 08.2007 - 12.2010 | Montfort Secondary School | | GCE O Level | |
| Work Experience | | | | |

01.2018 - Now Mo

Motic China Group Co., Ltd

Software Developer

Worked as a software developer in the Development Department, and mainly handle the following tasks:

- ➤ Using Android Studio to maintain the Android application:
 - To develop a new feature.
 - To fix the bugs.
 - To brief the updates to the Production Line, and train the stuff.
- ➤ Use Shell Scripting to patch the software on the Linux platform remotely.
- Self-learning Matlab, and take in charge of a new project with an American company, and handle the following tasks:
 - Code Conversion, which is: Converting Matlab Code to C++ Code.
 - Code Maintenance (Git), such as source code updates, the documentation maintenance.
 - Scrum Meeting, such as: to communicate with the other side to resolve the bugs, report the progress.

Worked as a software developer in the IBM Software Department – Deployment Automation Team, and mainly using Shell Scripting to handle the following tasks:

- Self-learning Jenkins then adopted a new authentication method on IBM Jenkins Server, e.g. LDAP (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol).
- ➤ Self-learning Docker, then work with the docker containers e.g. deploy the Docker containers.
- > Self-learning IBM WAS (WebSphere Application Server) and patching the server.
- ➤ Self-learning IBM BPM (Business Process Manager) and patching the server.
- > Self-learning IBM UCD (Urban Code Deployment) and use it as a tool for the deployment automation.
- ➤ Self-learning the software version control GitHub.

05.2017 - 07.2017

Motic China Group Co., Ltd

Intern

Worked as a software developer in the Software Development Department. Mainly doing the following tasks:

- ➤ Migrate a Visual Studio 2008 based program to Visual Studio 2013 based program.
- ➤ Integrate with Motic protection mechanism, e.g. hardware dongle and software license.
- Integrate with Motic hardware, e.g. the Motic camera series.
- ➤ Get familiar with the migration of the Matlab solution to C++ language based.

08.2015 - 11.2015

Project Manager

Gathered a team of five to provide services to a company. E.g. Android, IOS and web page development for their online ticket ordering system for the bus services.

06.2015-11.2014

S&Z Pte LTD.

Start up

Join a start-up software company which is launched by a friend from NTU. I played a part as a helper in recruitment and project planning.

| Awards | |
|--------|--|
| 2012 | Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Singapore Technologies Telemedia Prize |
| 2012 | Singapore Polytechnic - Director's Honour Roll |
| 2013 | Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Hutcabb Prize |
| 2013 | Singapore Polytechnic - Director's Honour Roll |
| 2014 | Singapore Polytechnic - Merit Award - Singapore Technologies Telemedia Prize |
| 2014 | Singapore Polytechnic - Diploma With Merit |
| 2018 | Nanyang Technological University – Degree with Honours (Merit) |
| | |

Skills & Abilities

Language Proficiency English and Chinese (Written & Spoken)

Programming Background Java, C, C++, C#, Python and Visual Basic.